<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on According to Ja-plan</title>
    <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on According to Ja-plan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 22:55:53 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>We Came All the Way to Japan for Denny&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/dennys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 22:55:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/dennys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we made a new friend from the hostel. His name is Heinz and he hung out
with us all day. We started our day by going to the Denny&amp;rsquo;s near our hostel for
breakfast. The food there was good, but very American, so we decided not to go
to Denny&amp;rsquo;s again after today. After breakfast, we headed to Shinjuku to see the
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.japan-guide.com/e/e3002.html&#34;&gt;Meiji Shrine&lt;/a&gt;. On the way, we stopped
by a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Book_Off&#34;&gt;Book Off&lt;/a&gt; to look for used video
games and books.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/meiji_shrine.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Meiji Shrine had a large gate outside of it.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        The Meiji Shrine had a large gate outside of it.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;After stopping by Book Off, we went to the Meiji Shrine, which was surrounded by
Yoyogi Park. It was really hot out in the park, but it was very beautiful and
had lots of trees. We went through the park and got to the Meiji Shrine, which
also looked really pretty. After visiting the shrine, Aaron and Heinz went to
see the lilac garden near the shrine, and Michelle and I went to the cafe in the
shrine. While we were in the cafe, we got peach jelly parfaits, which were very
refreshing because it was so hot out. We met back up with Aaron and Heinz, just
in time for them to go off to get ramen for lunch while Michelle and I went to
an arcade. Aaron and Heinz met back up with us at the arcade after they finished
lunch. We played Jubeat, Dance Dance Revolution, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Groove_Coaster&#34;&gt;Groove
Coaster&lt;/a&gt; at the arcade. Finally,
we went to get conveyor belt sushi for dinner and went back to the hostel.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/peach_parfait.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The peach jelly parfaits were very refreshing.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        The peach jelly parfaits were very refreshing.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Return of the Luggage</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/the-return-of-the-luggage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 23:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/the-return-of-the-luggage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We started out the day by grabbing a quick breakfast from 7-Eleven, then we
headed to Akihavara to look at all of the stores and arcades there. We started
out by going to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kanda_Shrine&#34;&gt;Kanda Shrine&lt;/a&gt;,
which is a shrine that caters to technophiles and geeks. We prayed at the shrine
and got fortunes there. Afterwards, we looked at some of the stores in Akihabara
selling anime merchandise and went to an arcade to play some of the crane games
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jubeat&#34;&gt;Jubeat&lt;/a&gt;. We even won a plushie from
one of the crane games!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/miku.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;We actually won something from a crane game!&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        We actually won something from a crane game!
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;At this point, it was noon, so we went back to the hostel to check if our
luggage had arrived there. Our suitcases were there, so we brought them back up
to our room and unpacked some of our things. After rejoicing about the return of
our suitcases, we went back to Akihabara for lunch, which we got at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://akb48cafeshops.com/akihabara/english&#34;&gt;AKB48
Cafe&lt;/a&gt;. After lunch, we looked at
more stores in Akihabara, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Don_Quijote_(store)&#34;&gt;Don
Quijote&lt;/a&gt;, a giant chain
store. Then we want back to an arcade to play more Jubeat and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dance_Dance_Revolution&#34;&gt;Dance Dance
Revolution&lt;/a&gt;. Finally,
after we got tired of the arcade, we went back to the hostel to do laundry and
sleep.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/return_of_luggage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;All of us celebrating the return of our luggage.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        All of us celebrating the return of our luggage.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad RNG in Tokyo</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/bad-rng/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 21:56:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/bad-rng/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We landed in the Haneda airport in Tokyo after a long 13 hour flight. We were a
bit tired from the flight, but ready to start our Japan adventure.
Unfortunately, our adventure was temporarily postponed because Air Canada lost
all of our luggage. We needed to wait in a line to fill out lost baggage forms
so the airline was made aware of our lost luggage. It looked like a whole
quarter of our flight was filling out similar forms, so I think Air Canada lost
a lot of bags from that flight. Eventually, we all filled out the forms and were
told that we would be contacted when they found our bags. We left the baggage
area of the airport, bought 3-day passes for the subway, picked up our pocket
wi-fi, and headed towards our hostel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On our way to the hostel, we tried to take out money from an ATM at a 7-Eleven
that we passed. We almost weren&amp;rsquo;t able to withdraw enough money for the hostel
because Michelle&amp;rsquo;s card got declined and Aaron reached his withdrawal limit for
the day, but together we were able to withdraw enough money. We finally made it
to &lt;a href=&#34;https://backpackersjapan.co.jp/citan/&#34;&gt;CITAN&lt;/a&gt;, the hostel we would be
staying at, and found that it was huge and pretty nice. We took a quick look
inside our room, then went out to buy some clothes at a nearby Uniqlo, since we
didn&amp;rsquo;t have our suitcases with us and we were wearing our pajamas on the flight.
We bought some clothes, including a One Piece graphic T-shirt that I got. On the
way back to the hostel, we stopped by a 7-Eleven to buy some snacks and
toiletries. After eating the snacks at the hostel, we all went to sleep early
because we were all tired.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/shibuya_crossing.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;A picture of Shibuya crossing, one of the busiest streets in Tokyo, when it is slightly less busy.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        A picture of Shibuya crossing, one of the busiest streets in Tokyo, when it is slightly less busy.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The next day, we all woke up at 6am because of jet lag. For breakfast we got
some onigiri from the 7-Eleven next door to our hostel and ate them at the
hostel. After breakfast, we headed to Shibuya to buy more clothes since we still
hadn&amp;rsquo;t received any updates about our luggage. We checked out the fancy clothing
stores in &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/109_(department_store)&#34;&gt;Shibuya 109&lt;/a&gt;,
went to the Uniqlo in Shibuya, and got lunch at a cafe. After exploring the
stores in Shibuya, we went to Shimokitazawa to look at all of the thrift stores
there. Finally, after having our fill of shopping, we wanted to get out of the
heat, so we headed back to Shibuya to see &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mary_and_the_Witch%27s_Flower&#34;&gt;Mary and the Witch&amp;rsquo;s
Flower&lt;/a&gt; in a movie
theater. I understood more of the movie than I thought I would, and was able to
follow most of it. We were hungry after the movie, so we went to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurant_Review-g1066456-d2496563-Reviews-Aoyama_Flower_Market_Tea_House-Shibuya_Tokyo_Tokyo_Prefecture_Kanto.html&#34;&gt;Aoyama
Flower Market
Teahouse&lt;/a&gt;
for dinner. We headed back to the hostel after dinner and discovered that we
would be getting our luggage back by noon the next day, so we were very happy
that night.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/flower_cafe.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Aaron had a lot of fun at the flower cafe.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        Aaron had a lot of fun at the flower cafe.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Creepy Psycho Hotel in Toronto</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/creepy-hotel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 08:10:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/creepy-hotel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was our first day of travel to get to Japan. After we woke up, we went out
to Target to get ice cream and gifts for Aaron&amp;rsquo;s cousin in Korea. We had to go
through the ballroom floor to get out of the hotel. They had all of the
speedruns on this floor and it was busy all week, but it was completely empty as
we walked through it today. After we got back to the hotel, it was time to go to
the airport, so we took the SGDQ shuttle there and checked in to our 2 hour
flight to Toronto. The flight went pretty smoothly, and we watched part of
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt5052448/&#34;&gt;Get Out&lt;/a&gt; on the plane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our flight, we had an 18 hour layover in Toronto before our flight to
Tokyo, and we needed to figure out how to fill it. We tried to check our bags
for the Tokyo flight, but the earliest the airport would let us check our bags
was 4 hours before the flight. Since we had to hold on to our bags for the next
14 hours, we decided to try to book a room at a hotel near the airport for the
night. We chose the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Hotel_Review-g154996-d188214-Reviews-Days_Inn_Toronto_West_Mississauga-Mississauga_Ontario.html&#34;&gt;Days Inn Toronto West
Mississauga&lt;/a&gt;,
which turned out to be a bad choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then we reached this beautiful hotel! With oddly shaped stains on the
carpet, a shower that screams like a banshee, windows that&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t look like
windows, lights that were stapled in crooked to the walls, ominous holes where
paintings were ripped off of walls, and the lovely hum of everyone talking in
the hallways or nearby rooms. -Michelle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hotel advertised a shuttle service from the airport, but the shuttles didn&amp;rsquo;t
run on a regular schedule, so we needed to call the hotel to ask for a shuttle.
The only problem was that none of us had international calling on our phones. We
ended up finding a pay phone in the airport and tried calling from that, but we
just got put on hold and couldn&amp;rsquo;t talk to anyone at the hotel. Since we weren&amp;rsquo;t
able to book the shuttle, we tried to get an Uber from the airport to the hotel,
but Uber wasn&amp;rsquo;t available in that area yet. All of our other options were
exhausted, so we had to get a cab from the airport to the hotel. The cab ride
cost us an arm and a leg, but we managed to get to the hotel and check in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, this place is just like the hotel from Psycho! -Michelle &lt;br /&gt;
~&lt;em&gt;instantaneous roaring of pipes fills the room&lt;/em&gt;~&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I&amp;rsquo;m convinced this is a burial site for bodies that were stolen from
airport -Michelle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hotel looked really creepy, like it was taken straight out of
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0054215/&#34;&gt;Psycho&lt;/a&gt;. After we got situated in the
hotel room, we were really tired, so we finished watching Get Out and went to
sleep.  The next morning, we went to the tiny breakfast provided by the hotel,
then took the hotel shuttle to the airport. We got to the airport 4 hours early
to check our bags for the flight, but the line to check-in took almost 2 hours
to get through. While we were waiting until we could board the airplane, we
visited the duty-free shop at the airport, contemplated buying maple syrup, and
looked for poutine but were unable to find any. Finally, we boarded the plane
for out 13 hour flight to Tokyo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bets on if the room is haunted? -Michelle &lt;br /&gt;
~&lt;em&gt;lights flicker ominously&lt;/em&gt;~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 7: Super Special Bonus Extra Game</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 08:07:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SGDQ raises money to donate to charity, and yesterday they hit 1 million dollars
in donations, so today they had a cake party to celebrate and thank all
of the attendees. We woke up just in time for the cake party, so we went
downstairs to get some cake. Afterwards, we went to Target to buy some food, and
I also got a new tank top and Deadpool-patterned button-down shirt, along with a
pair of shorts.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/cake_party.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;We had lots of cake at the cake party.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        We had lots of cake at the cake party.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/deadpool_shirt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Featured: me in my beautiful new button-down.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        Featured: me in my beautiful new button-down.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;After Target, we went back to the hotel room and ordered food for lunch and
dinner, since we would be watching speedruns for the rest of the day. While we
waited for the food to arrive, we watched the speedrun of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLxG7HQxMIfYrkzSzsjGE7a9bIghP43Y9H&#34;&gt;Super Panga
World&lt;/a&gt;,
a set of almost impossible custom levels created for Super Mario World. The food
arrived and we ate it, then we went down to the speedrunning room to watch runs
of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Mario_64&#34;&gt;Super Mario 64&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_Majora%27s_Mask&#34;&gt;The
Legend of Zelda: Majora&amp;rsquo;s
Mask&lt;/a&gt;. There
was a bonus incentive that required $100,000 of donations for a speedrun of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_Breath_of_the_Wild&#34;&gt;The
Legend of Zelda: Breath of the
Wild&lt;/a&gt;
that was met, so there was also a speedrun of Breath of the Wild. After the
Breath of the Wild incentive was met, there was another $200,000 incentive for a
single person speedrun of the co-op mode in &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Portal_2&#34;&gt;Portal
2&lt;/a&gt;, which was also met, so there was a
super bonus speedrun of Portal 2. Finally, the last speedrun of SGDQ was one of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/EarthBound&#34;&gt;Earthbound&lt;/a&gt;. After that speedrun, we
went to sleep, since we had a long flight the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 6: I&#39;ll Make an SGDQ Out of You</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 18:57:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We woke up at noon today because we stayed up pretty late last night watching
speedruns. We woke up just in time for a pizza party sponsored by SGDQ, and we
went downstairs to get free pizza for lunch. After eating our pizza, we went to
the speedrunning room to see a run of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kingdom_Hearts_II&#34;&gt;Kingdom Hearts
II&lt;/a&gt;. There was a Disney
sing-a-long during the speedrun, so we got to listen to the runners sing &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZSS5dEeMX64&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll
Make a Man Out of You&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SXKlJuO07eM&#34;&gt;Part of
Your World&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-kl4hJ4j48s&#34;&gt;A Whole New
World&lt;/a&gt;,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VuJTqmpBnI0&#34;&gt;Gaston&lt;/a&gt;, and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U3NoDEu7kpg&#34;&gt;Hellfire&lt;/a&gt;. After the run, we went
to the arcade room to play &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jubeat&#34;&gt;Jubeat&lt;/a&gt;,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dungeons_%26_Dragons:_Shadow_over_Mystara&#34;&gt;D&amp;amp;D&lt;/a&gt;,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sunset_Riders&#34;&gt;Sunset Riders&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dance_Dance_Revolution&#34;&gt;Dance Dance
Revolution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After playing games in the arcade room for a while, we went back to the
speedrunning room to see Super Mario Warpless Relay Race, which involved 3 teams
of 5 speedrunners each racing through 5 &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Mario&#34;&gt;Super
Mario&lt;/a&gt; games. It was a long race, but
all of the teams managed to finish within 8 minutes of each other, which was
amazing. Next, we watched the Metroid block which included &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metroid_Fusion&#34;&gt;Metroid
Fusion&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Super_Metroid&#34;&gt;Super
Metroid&lt;/a&gt;. We went back to the
arcade room to play more D&amp;amp;D, Jubeat, and DDR, then we went up to the room to
get ready for bed. Right before we went to sleep, Michelle and I showed Aaron
the first episode of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rave_Master&#34;&gt;Groove Master
Rave&lt;/a&gt;, a hilariously bad anime, since
he hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen it before.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 5: Insert Potato Joke Here</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:57:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we woke up kinda late at 11am, and went down to the speedrunning room to
see a run of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shadow_of_the_Colossus&#34;&gt;Shadow of the
Colossus&lt;/a&gt;. We wanted to
get International Drivers Permits today so we could do a tour of Tokyo on
go-karts once we got to Japan, so after the run we went next door to the
Minneapolis AAA to get the permits.  After getting the permits, we went back to
the speedrunning room to see a run of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Portal_(video_game)&#34;&gt;Portal&lt;/a&gt;. We had some free
time before the next speedrun that we wanted to see, so we went back to the room
to hang out, then got dinner at the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was the beginning of runs of some of the most popular games at SGDQ. We
started with the Mario Kart block, which included &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mario_Kart_64&#34;&gt;Mario Kart
64&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mario_Kart_Wii&#34;&gt;Mario Kart
Wii&lt;/a&gt;. Next, there was a tetris
block, which included an 8-way race of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tetris:_The_Grand_Master&#34;&gt;Tetris: The Grand
Master&lt;/a&gt;, a 2-players,
1-controller race of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tetris:_The_Grand_Master&#34;&gt;Tetris: The Grand
Master&lt;/a&gt;, a run of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tetris:_The_Grand_Master&#34;&gt;Tetris: The Grand
Master&lt;/a&gt; in Rev Mode
(everything upside down), and a run of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tetris:_The_Grand_Master#Tetris:_The_Grand_Master_3_-_Terror-Instinct&#34;&gt;Tetris: The Grand Master 3: Terror
Instinct&lt;/a&gt;.
After that, there was a Legend of Zelda block including a swordless run of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_A_Link_to_the_Past&#34;&gt;The
Legend of Zelda: A Link to the
Past&lt;/a&gt;
(which was amazing), a run of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zelda_II:_The_Adventure_of_Link&#34;&gt;Zelda 2: The Adventure of
Link&lt;/a&gt;, and a
2-way race of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_Link%27s_Awakening&#34;&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Link&amp;rsquo;s Awakening
DX&lt;/a&gt;.
This block started very late, so we were very tired during it. We decided to
skip the run of Zelda 2 and take a 45 minute catnap in the room instead. We
managed to wake up for Link&amp;rsquo;s Awakening, and stayed through the race of &lt;a href=&#34;http://store.steampowered.com/app/554000/Crypt_of_the_NecroDancer_AMPLIFIED/&#34;&gt;Crypt
of the NecroDancer:
AMPLIFIED&lt;/a&gt;.
It was practically the morning by the time the Crypt of the NecroDancer race was
over, so we all went back up to the room to go to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 4: I am an American Boulevard</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 16:57:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, there were no runs that we were very interested in seeing in the morning
or afternoon, so we were able to wake up late. Aaron needed to do work today,
but Michelle and I wanted to visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mallofamerica.com/&#34;&gt;Mall of
America&lt;/a&gt;, so we looked up how to get there. We
wanted to try to bike there using &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.niceridemn.org/&#34;&gt;Nice Ride&lt;/a&gt;, a
bikesharing program in Minneapolis, but there were no Nice Ride stations close
to the mall.  We ended up not being able to bike there, so we took the tram.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/tram.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;We rode on the tram to get to the Mall of America&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        We rode on the tram to get to the Mall of America
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The Mall of America was huge! It had an indoor amusement park, aquarium, mini
golf, and a food court. It also had the best digital directory user interface
I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. We spent most of the day wandering around the mall.  First we
went to Barnes and Noble to look at all of the books. Next we went to both of
the Gamestops in the mall to see what games they had. Then we went through the
Nickelodeon amusement park, the Crayola store, and the Lego store.  We were
getting hungry after this, so we went to the food court and had grilled cheese
for lunch. We wanted ice cream for dessert, but were too full after lunch, so we
went to Barnes and Noble to hang out and read books while we waited to digest
our food. After about an hour at Barnes and Noble, we were hungry again, so we
got ice cream from the mall. Then we went back to the hotel for a night of
watching speedruns.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/mall_amusement_park.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The mall was so huge it had its own amusement park&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        The mall was so huge it had its own amusement park
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We made it back to the hotel just in time for the Megaman X block of speedruns,
which included &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Man_X6&#34;&gt;Megaman X6&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Man_X_(video_game)&#34;&gt;Megaman
X&lt;/a&gt;, a 4-way race of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Man_X2&#34;&gt;Megaman X2&lt;/a&gt;, and a 2-way race of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mega_Man_X3&#34;&gt;Megaman X3&lt;/a&gt;. Next, there was a run
of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_Twilight_Princess&#34;&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Twilight
Princess&lt;/a&gt;.
After this, Aaron was tired so he went to sleep, but Michelle and I stayed up
for the run of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Elder_Scrolls_IV:_Oblivion&#34;&gt;The Elder Scrolls IV:
Oblivion&lt;/a&gt;, which
was great. After that, we went to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 3: Five Star Music, Two Star Game</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 16:56:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we woke up extra early to see a speedrun of the game &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.iambreadgame.com/overview/&#34;&gt;I am
Bread&lt;/a&gt;, a weird game about bread that one
review said &amp;ldquo;[has] five stars for music, but two for the game&amp;rdquo;.  Afterwards,
Aaron went to the cafe to do work and Michelle and I went back to the hotel
room, had breakfast, and watched an episode of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tsurezure_Children&#34;&gt;Tsurezure
Children&lt;/a&gt; while we were
waiting for the pizza we had ordered the previous day. We finally got our pizza
and ate a few slices for lunch. I was very tired at this point, so I took a nap
while Michelle went to the speedrunning room to see runs of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.brothersthegame.com/&#34;&gt;Brothers: A Tale of
Two Sons&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banjo-Kazooie&#34;&gt;Banjo-Kazooie&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I woke up from my nap just in time for the block of Pokemon speed runs including
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pok%C3%A9mon_Puzzle_League&#34;&gt;Pokemon Puzzle
League&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pok%C3%A9mon_HeartGold_and_SoulSilver&#34;&gt;Pokemon
HeartGold/SoulSilver&lt;/a&gt;.
There were no more runs that night that we wanted to see, so Michelle, Aaron,
and I went to a bar to celebrate the 4th of July and do some bar trivia.
Unfortunately, trivia was cancelled that night, but we were still able to go to
the bar and have some drinks. After having fun at the bar, we headed back to the
hotel and Aaron and I went to the speedrunning room to watch a quick run of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dishonored_2&#34;&gt;Dishonored 2&lt;/a&gt;. After the run, we
were all exhausted, so we went back up to the room to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 2: Peanut Butter and Banana Sandwiches</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 09:54:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This morning we were planning on waking up at 9:30am, but we were woken up at
8:30 because that&amp;rsquo;s when housekeeping wanted to clean the room. After we became
more awake, Aaron went to a cafe to do work for the day (he&amp;rsquo;s working from home
this week, so he&amp;rsquo;s not going to any speedruns during work hours). Michelle and I
went down to the hotel lobby to ask if SGDQ provided free breakfast. There was
no free breakfast from the hotel, but today the convention organizers got free
donuts for the attendees. We got there right when the donuts arrived, so we got
our pick of them. After finishing our donuts, we went to the speedrunning room
to see the runs of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crash_Bandicoot_(video_game)&#34;&gt;Crash
Bandicoot&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spyro:_Year_of_the_Dragon&#34;&gt;Spyro: Year of the
Dragon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There weren&amp;rsquo;t any more runs that we wanted to see for a while after this, so
Michelle and I went back up to the room to work on our blogs. We were also
getting hungry for lunch at this point, so after working for a bit we headed
next door to Target to scavenge up some food. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have a fridge,
microwave, or any way to boil water in the room, so our options for food were
quite limited. We ended up getting peanut butter, nutella, bread, bananas, and
apples for sandwiches, since none of those ingredients requires a fridge or
microwave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Target, we went back to the room and ate lunch. Aaron came back from
working soon after this, and we went down to see a block of Sonic speedruns that
included &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sonic_Generations&#34;&gt;Sonic Generations&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sonic_Colors&#34;&gt;Sonic Colors&lt;/a&gt;. We came back up
to the room to eat a dinner consisting of peanut butter and banana sandwiches.
While we were in the room I managed to beat &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Legend_of_Zelda:_Breath_of_the_Wild&#34;&gt;Legend of Zelda: Breath of the
Wild&lt;/a&gt;, a
game I had been playing for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After dinner, we went back down to the speedrunning room to see &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mirror%27s_Edge&#34;&gt;Mirror&amp;rsquo;s
Edge&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mirror%27s_Edge_Catalyst&#34;&gt;Mirror&amp;rsquo;s Edge
Catalyst&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donkey_Kong_64&#34;&gt;Donkey
Kong 64&lt;/a&gt;. We took a short break
after Donkey Kong to go back to the room. Aaron went to sleep because he needed
to wake up early to do more work, but Michelle and I went back down to the
speedrunning room to see &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jet_Set_Radio_Future&#34;&gt;Jet Set Radio
Future&lt;/a&gt;. During this run, I
got hungry for pizza, so we decided to order two pizzas to be delivered the next
day so we didn&amp;rsquo;t need to eat peanut butter and banana sandwiches for every meal.
We got bored of the Jet Set radio future run, so after a while we went back to
the room. We weren&amp;rsquo;t quite tired yet, so Michelle showed me an episode of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rave_Master&#34;&gt;The
Groove Adventure Rave&lt;/a&gt;, a weird and
hilarious anime. Finally, we went to sleep to get ready for another day of SGDQ.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGDQ Day 1: This Shopping Mall is Empty</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 23:44:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/sgdq-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today began at the early hour of 4:30am, when I had to drag myself out of bed
and go to the airport with my parents. After a teary goodbye, I was quickly off
on a plane to my first destination: Minneapolis, MN. My flight went really
smoothly, and I landed in the Minneapolis airport two and a half hours later.
Things were going well for me, but not so much for my friends. Their flight from
Chicago was delayed for an hour and a half, so instead of landing at the airport
half an hour before me, they landed a full hour after me. Eventually, we all met
up at the airport and caught the SGDQ shuttle to the hotel we would be staying
at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got to the hotel just in time to drop our bags off, check in for SGDQ, and go
to the speedrunning room before the first game started.  The convention kicked
off with a really interesting speedrun: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twitch.tv/halfcoordinated&#34;&gt;a
speedrunner&lt;/a&gt; beat &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nier:_Automata&#34;&gt;Nier:
Automata&lt;/a&gt; using only one hand. The
speedrunner was disabled and had limited use of his right hand, so he learned
how to play the game using only his left hand. This was a fun speedrun to watch,
especially since it was so unique.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/minneapolis_hotel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;A picture of our hotel in Minneapolis. Michelle for scale.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        A picture of our hotel in Minneapolis. Michelle for scale.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;After the speedrun was over, we realized we were all starving, so we went
outside to find something to eat and explore Minneapolis. We didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it
at the time, but this was much harder to do than we thought. First of all, there
was massive construction happening on the streets surrounding the hotel, so it
was hard to get anywhere outside. Luckily, there were skyways connecting the
hotel and all of the buildings surrounding it, so we could travel between all of
the buildings. There was a shopping mall next door to the hotel, so we decided
to go there to find something for lunch.  What we didn&amp;rsquo;t realize is that almost
every store in Minneapolis closes for the weekend. The mall was like a ghost
town because almost all of the stores there were closed and there were barely
any people there. To make it worse, there weren&amp;rsquo;t any directories or signs, so
it was very easy to get lost. We wandered around for about an hour, but we
couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any place to get food that was open and didn&amp;rsquo;t have a line
extending out the door. Eventually, we just camped out in an empty hallway in
the shopping mall and ate some of the breakfast bars that I packed for the trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time we got up from the hallway and got back to the hotel, it was almost
time for dinner. After our unsuccessful excursion, we decided that it would be
better to order food to the hotel than to try to go out again. While we ate, we
watched &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moana_(2016_film)&#34;&gt;Moana&lt;/a&gt; since Aaron had
never seen it before. After dinner, we went back to the speedrunning room to
watch speedruns of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Diddy_Kong_Racing&#34;&gt;Diddy Kong
Racing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Luigi%27s_Mansion&#34;&gt;Luigi&amp;rsquo;s
Mansion&lt;/a&gt;. There were more
interesting speedruns after those, but we got bored of sitting and watching
things, so we decided to explore the game rooms set up for the convention. We
found the arcade game room and stayed there for a good hour.  Michelle and I
played against each other at
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tekken_(video_game)&#34;&gt;Tekken&lt;/a&gt; while Aaron tried
his hand at &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donkey_Kong_(video_game)&#34;&gt;Donkey
Kong&lt;/a&gt;. Afterwards, we
all played &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Battletoads_Arcade&#34;&gt;Battletoads&lt;/a&gt;, one
of the hardest arcade games ever, and managed to beat it.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/janky_fridge.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;We had leftovers from dinner but no fridge to store them in, so we improvised.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        We had leftovers from dinner but no fridge to store them in, so we improvised.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We headed back to the hotel room, but we were all exhausted at this point, so we
were all falling asleep while we were hanging out there. There was one final
speedrun we wanted to see before we went to bed, so we rallied and went back to
the speedrunning room to watch the run of
&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%C5%8Ckami&#34;&gt;Okami&lt;/a&gt; before we finally crashed for
the night. All in all, this was a great day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 20:02:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://according-to-japlan.tk/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my travel blog! This is a blog to describe the trip I am taking with
two of my best friends from college during the summer before I start work. First
we&amp;rsquo;re staying in Minneapolis for a week for &lt;a href=&#34;https://gamesdonequick.com/&#34;&gt;Summer Games Done
Quick&lt;/a&gt;, then we&amp;rsquo;re headed to Japan for 4 weeks, and
finally to South Korea for a week.  It should be a great trip!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://according-to-japlan.tk/img/selfie.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;This is us! From left to right there&amp;#39;s Michelle, Aaron, and me.&#34; /&gt;
    
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
        This is us! From left to right there&amp;#39;s Michelle, Aaron, and me.
        
            
        
        &lt;/p&gt; 
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>